Family vs. Frat
Neighbors is a comedy film directed by Nicholas Stoller.
A couple with a newborn baby face unexpected difficulties after
they are forced to live next to a fraternity house.
Mac Radner, played by Seth Rogen.
Teddy Sanders, played by Zac Efron.
Kelly Radner, played by Rose Byrne.
Pete Regazolli, played by Dave Franco.
Scoonie Schofield, played by Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
Garf, played by Jerrod Carmichael.
Neighbors (released in some countries as Bad Neighbours) is a 2014 American
comedy film directed by Nicholas Stoller and written by Andrew J.
Cohen and Brendan O'Brien.
The film stars Seth Rogen and Zac Efron, with Rose Byrne, Dave
Franco, and Christopher Mintz-Plasse in supporting roles.
The plot follows a couple who come into conflict with a fraternity that has
recently moved in next door, which leads them into an all-out war.
The film premiered at South by Southwest on March 8, 2014, and
was released on May 9 in the United States.
The film received generally positive reviews, with praise aimed at Efron's breakout performance, and was a commercial
success, grossing over $270 million worldwide, and became Rogen's highest-grossing live-action film.
A sequel, Neighbors 2: Sorority Rising, was released on May 20, 2016, with Stoller
returning to direct, and much of the cast reprising their roles.
The film explores themes of baby, routine, house party, parenting, family.
The tone is lighthearted.